- This song is called
"Hey There, Delilah."
Everyone always asks me if
there's really a Delilah
and if that's really her name.
And yes, there is a real Delilah,
and her name actually is
Delilah, believe it or not.
But the story behind the
song, we never dated.
It was just a girl that I met
that went to school in New York City,
and
I just thought she was very pretty,
and she inspired me to write this song.
So this is "Hey There, Delilah."
(upbeat music)
♪ Hey there, Delilah ♪
♪ What's it like in New York City ♪
♪ I'm a thousand miles away ♪
♪ But girl, tonight you look so pretty ♪
♪ Yes, you do ♪
♪ Times Square can't
shine as bright as you ♪
♪ I swear it's true ♪
♪ Hey there, Delilah ♪
♪ Don't you worry about the distance ♪
♪ I'm right there if you get lonely ♪
♪ Give this song another listen ♪
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Listen to my voice ♪
♪ It's my disguise ♪
♪ I'm by your side ♪
♪ Oh, it's what you do to me ♪
♪ What you do to me ♪
♪ Hey there, Delilah ♪
♪ I know times are getting hard ♪
♪ Just believe me, girl ♪
♪ Someday I'll pay the
bills with this guitar ♪
♪ We'll have it good ♪
♪ We'll have the life we knew we would ♪
♪ My word is good ♪
♪ Hey there, Delilah ♪
♪ I've got so much left to say ♪
♪ If every simple song I wrote to you ♪
♪ Would take your breath away ♪
♪ I'd write it all ♪
♪ Even more in love with me you'd fall ♪
♪ We'd have it all ♪
♪ Oh, it's what you do to me ♪
♪ A thousand miles seems pretty far ♪
♪ But they've got planes
and trains and cars ♪
♪ I'd walk to you if I had no other way ♪
♪ Our friends will all make fun of us ♪
♪ And we'll just laugh along ♪
♪ Because we know that none
of them have felt this way ♪
♪ Delilah, I can promise you ♪
♪ By the time we get through ♪
♪ The world will never ever be the same ♪
♪ You're to blame ♪
♪ Hey there, Delilah ♪
♪ You be good, and don't you miss me ♪
♪ Two more years and you'll
be done with school ♪
♪ I'll be making history, like I do ♪
♪ You'll know it's all because of you ♪
♪ We can do whatever we want to ♪
♪ Hey there, Delilah, here's to you ♪
♪ This one's for you ♪
♪ Oh, it's what you do to me ♪
♪ What you do to me ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, whoa ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪